Inventory of the Ginetta Sagan papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Humanitas, 1976-1981
  - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 15: 12-14)
    Includes translation of a 1945 letter from Tiberio Panzini to GS and an invitation to the White House
  - Resignation letter by GS, 1982 April 20 (Box-folder 15: 15)
- Pierre Rigoulot writing, 1980 (Box-folder 16: 1)
- Clippings, 1978-1981
  - International Herald Tribune, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Los Angeles Times, 1980 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Le Matin, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Le Monde, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 16: 5)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur, 1978 (Box-folder 16: 6-7)
- Censorship, 1982 (Box-folder 16: 8)
- Collected articles on current world events, 1983 (Box-folder 17: 1)
- Vietnam, 1973-1981
  - Violations of Human Rights in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, April 30, 1975-April 30, 1983, by GS (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Buddhism, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Encyclopedia entry on Vietnam, undated (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Anti-war activists, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Collected articles and clippings, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 17: 6-9)
  - Media, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Vietnam Digest, 1979 May-July (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Assorted commentary, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Post-Vietnam Era, 1980 (Box-folder 17: 13)
    Includes annotations by GS
  - Southeast Asia Chronicle, 1977 (Box-folder 17: 14)
  - Southeast Asia Record, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 17: 15)
  - Pham Van Dong clipping, 1978 September 24 (Box-folder 17: 16)
  - The Oregonian clipping, 1977 December 6 (Box-folder 17: 17)
  - New York Times clippings, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 17: 18)
- Argentina clipping, 1980 October 4 (Box-folder 17: 19)
- Country Reports on Human Rights Practices for 1982, Department of State report, 1983 February (Box-folder 18: 1)
- Collected articles on current world events, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 18: 2-4)
- Cambodia file, 1977-1984
  - Noam Chomsky, François Ponchaud, and Robert Silvers correspondence on Ponchaud's Cambodia: Year Zero, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - World Without War Council correspondence, 1984 July 26 (Box-folder 19: 1)
- Amnesty International, 1972-1985
  - General, 1972-1985
    - Adoption groups, 1983 (Box-folder 19: 2)
    - Amnesty Action, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 19: 3-4)
    - Anacapa Fund, 1985 (Box-folder 19: 5)
    - Annual general meetings, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 19: 6-10)
    - Art auction, undated (Box-folder 19: 11)
    - Artists for Amnesty, undated (Box-folder 19: 12)
    - Artwork for Prisoner of Conscience Week, 1981 (Box-folder 19: 13)
    - Bay Area Legal Support Network, 1984 (Box-folder 19: 14)
    - Bernstein, Leonard, special event, 1982 July (Box-folder 19: 15)
      Includes photographs of GS and Bernstein
    - Bills and receipts, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 19: 16)
    - Board materials, 1984 (Box-folder 19: 17)
    - Board meeting, 1984 January-February (Box-folder 19: 18)
    - Board election results, 1984 June 13 (Box-folder 19: 19)
    - Board coordination groups, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 20: 1)
    - Board files, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 20: 2)
    - Barber, James David, correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 20: 3)
    - Board retreat, 1983 (Box-folder 20: 4)
    - Board meeting, 1983 November (Box-folder 20: 5)
    - Budget, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 20: 6-7)
    - Budget, fundraising, and programs, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 20: 8)
    - Bylaws, 1977, 1983 (Box-folder 20: 9)
    - Cambodia Witness Symposium, 1983 (Box-folder 20: 10)
    - Canadian section, 1985 (Box-folder 20: 11-12)
    - Civil disobedience, 1984 (Box-folder 20: 13)
    - Commendations, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 20: 14)
    - Committees, 1984 June (Box-folder 20: 15)
    - Computer project, 1982 (Box-folder 20: 16)
    - Congressional visits, 1985 (Box-folder 20: 17)
    - Contributions, undated (Box-folder 20: 18)
    - Coordination groups, 1985 (Box-folder 20: 19)
    - Death penalty, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 21: 1)
    - Democratic convention, 1983 (Box-folder 21: 2)
    - Democratization of membership, 1983 (Box-folder 21: 3)
    - Discussion papers on torture, undated (Box-folder 21: 4)
    - Documents on structure, 1982 (Box-folder 21: 5)
    - Executive committee meeting, 1984 April 27 (Box-folder 21: 6)
    - FBI misconduct press release, 1981 October 14 (Box-folder 21: 7)
    - Film script outline, A Candle in the Dark, 1983 July (Box-folder 21: 8)
    - Financial statements, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 21: 9)
    - Friends of Amnesty International, 1983 (Box-folder 21: 10-12)
    - Fundraising letters, 1984 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    - Group 19, 1981-1985
      - New member guide, 1985 (Box-folder 21: 14)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 21: 15)
      - Adopted prisoner program, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 21: 16-17)
      - Prisoner of Conscience Week at Stanford, 1981 (Box-folder 21: 18)
      - Historical file, 1972 (Box-folder 21: 19)
      - Letters to members, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 21: 20)
      - Financial, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 21: 21)
      - Bills and receipts, 1981 (Box-folder 21: 22)
    - Hammarberg, Thomas, correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 22: 1)
    - Healey, Jack, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 22: 2-3)
    - Health professionals, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 4)
    - Hinkley, David, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 22: 5)
    - Historical, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 22: 6)
    - Hoffman, Paul, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - Human rights, 1984 (Box-folder 22: 8)
    - Ivan Morris Fund, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 9)
    - International Council Meeting, 1983, 1985
      - Developing countries, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 10)
      - Fundraising, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 11)
      - 16th International Council, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 12)
      - 17th International Council, 1985 (Box-folder 22: 13)
    - India mission, 1984 (Box-folder 22: 14)
    - International Secretariat, units and departments, 1984 March 26 (Box-folder 22: 15)
    - International Executive Committee, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 22: 16)
    - Joiner, Lynne, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 22: 17)
    - Labor News, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 18)
    - London, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 22: 19)
    - Los Angeles office, 1982 (Box-folder 22: 20-21)
    - Los Angeles Banned Film Festival, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 22: 22)
    - Membership training project, 1985 (Box-folder 22: 23)
    - Matchbox, 1976-1977, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 24)
    - Matchbox correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 23: 1)
    - Meese, Ed, meeting, 1984 October 16 (Box-folder 23: 2)
    - Monthly mailings, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 23: 3-8)
    - National sections, 1981 (Box-folder 23: 9)
    - Newspaper articles, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 23: 10-11)
    - Non-governmental organizations, 1985 (Box-folder 23: 12)
    - Personnel, 1985 (Box-folder 23: 13)
    - Pope John Paul II, 1981 (Box-folder 23: 14)
    - Prisoner data questionnaires, undated (Box-folder 23: 15-16)
      In English and Spanish
    - Prisoner of Conscience Week, 1981, 1984 (Box-folder 23: 17-19)
    - Przeworski, Joanne Fox, 1984 (Box-folder 23: 20)
    - Publications, 1983 (Box-folder 23: 21)
    - Publicity and promotion, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 23: 22-23)
    - Regional conference, 1983 February 18-20 (Box-folder 23: 24)
    - Roebuck, Derek, 1978 (Box-folder 23: 25)
    - RMC list, undated (Box-folder 23: 26)
    - Regional conference, 1984 March 18-19 (Box-folder 23: 27)
    - Matchbox, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 23: 28)
    - James David Barber correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 24: 1)
    - Secretarial help, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 2)
    - Sociologists list, undated (Box-folder 24: 3)
    - Southern Regional Newsletter of AIUSA, 1985 June (Box-folder 24: 4)
    - Statute of Amnesty International, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 5)
    - Swiss section, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 24: 6)
    - Symbolic action and personal commitment, undated (Box-folder 24: 7)
    - Tax exempt letter, undated (Box-folder 24: 8)
    - United Nations 40th Anniversary Conference, 1985 (Box-folder 24: 9)
    - Universal amnesty, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 10)
    - United States Human Rights policy, 1984 May (Box-folder 24: 11)
    - West coast office materials, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 24: 12)
    - Women, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 13)
    - Women in prison, 1975 March (Box-folder 24: 14)
    - Writing for rights, undated (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Campaign Against Torture, 1975-1985
    - Briefing, 1984 April (Box-folder 24: 16)
    - Workshop on human rights, 1975 November-December (Box-folder 24: 17)
    - Bulletins, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 24: 18)
    - Cambodia, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 19)
    - Committee, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24: 20)
    - Congressional testimony, 1984 June (Box-folder 24: 21)
    - Fundraising letter, 1976 (Box-folder 24: 22)
    - Campaign correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 23)
    - Draft convention against torture, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 24)
    - Leaflet, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 25)
    - The Ides of March, screenplay by Bill Fertik, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 26)
    - Mental health in Uruguay, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - Geneva conference, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 2-6)
    - Geneva conference, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 1-3)
    - Racine, Wisconsin conference, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 4)
    - "The Next Campaign Against Torture" by Thomas Hammarberg, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 5)
    - "Torture: How to Make the International Convention Effective,", 1980 (Box-folder 26: 6)
    - Digests, 1983 July (Box-folder 26: 7)
    - Greek government, 1984 (Box-folder 26: 8)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 26: 9)
    - Medical information, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 26: 10)
    - Medical personnel in prison, 1976 June 30 (Box-folder 26: 11)
    - Clippings, 1984 (Box-folder 26: 12)
    - Plans, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 26: 13)
    - Plan and budget, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 14)
    - Photographs of victims for torture campaign, 1970s-early 1980s (Box-folder 26: 15)
      Includes index to photographs
    - Press releases, 1984 (Box-folder 26: 16)
    - Project for former presidents Carter and Ford, 1984 (Box-folder 26: 17)
    - Proposal for the Campaign for the Abolition of Torture, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 1)
    - Press releases, 1973, 1984 (Box-folder 27: 2-3)
    - Prospectus for conference on torture, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 4)
    - Racine, Wisconsin conference, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 5)
    - Rizza, Nick, correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 6)
    - Testimony on torture submitted to U.S. Congress, 1984 May (Box-folder 27: 7)
    - Time clipping, 1984 April 16 (Box-folder 27: 8)
    - Torture notes, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 27: 9)
    - Twelve point program for the abolition of torture, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 10)
    - Working papers, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 27: 11)
    - Urgent Action, 1985 (Box-folder 27: 12-13)
  - Fundraising, 1974-1985
    - Donors, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 28: 1-6)
    - Donors (cont'd.), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 29: 1-4)
    - Group 19 lists, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 29: 5)
      Includes photographs of GS
    - Festival of Forbidden Films, 1984 (Box-folder 29: 6-7)
      Clippings, correspondence, and press releases
    - Leonard Bernstein fundraising event, 1982 (Box-folder 29: 8)
    - Honorary committee, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 29: 9)
    - Fundraiser, Houston, Texas, 1983 July (Box-folder 29: 10)
    - 25th Anniversary Committee, 1985 (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - Lists of Friends of Amnesty International, 1985 (Box-folder 30: 2-3)
    - Donors, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 30: 4-8)
      Includes materials relating to the Festival of Forbidden Films
  - Routine correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 31: 1-2)
    Two accordion files
- Organizations and people file, 1978-1985
  Includes correspondence, printed matter, clippings, and collected articles
  - Ackerman, Harry, 1982 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Afghanistan conference, 1983 December (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - AIPAC, 1984 (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1983 (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - American Committee for Human Rights, undated (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - Angelini, Arnaldo, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Anti-nuclear movement, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - Aposporos, George T., 1983 (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - Aquino, Benigno, 1983 (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - Baez, Joan, undated (Box-folder 32: 11)
    Flyer advertising a Baez event
  - Bay Area Council for Soviet Jewry, undated (Box-folder 32: 12)
  - "Bigotry of the Modern Breed," by James C. Williams, 1980 July 7 (Box-folder 32: 13)
  - Carey, Steve, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 32: 14)
  - Carroll, Sherman, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 32: 15)
  - Casey, William, Commonwealth Club speech, 1984 April 3 (Box-folder 32: 16)
  - Cherne, Leo, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 32: 17)
  - Committee of Concerned Scientists, 1983 (Box-folder 32: 18)
  - Congressional Record, 1985 (Box-folder 32: 19-20)
  - Council of the Americas, 1984 (Box-folder 32: 21)
  - Council of Europe, 1982-1983 and undated (Box-folder 32: 22)
  - CROW (Center for Research on Women), undated (Box-folder 32: 23)
  - Dembinski, Piotr, early 1980s (Box-folder 32: 24)
  - Fallaci, Oriana, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 32: 25)
  - Fonda, Jane, 1970-1984 (Box-folder 32: 26)
    Includes photocopy of Fonda letter to Baez
  - Freedom at Issue, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 32: 27)
  - Fédération internationale des droits de l'homme, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Gliksman, Michael, 1983 (Box-folder 33: 2)
    Includes compact sound cassette titled "The Holocaust Survivor Project"
  - Griffiths, Ann Mills (National League of Families of American Prisoners and Missing in Southeast Asia), 1970-1985 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Harrison, Scott, 1981 (Box-folder 33: 4)
    Master's thesis on AIUSA
  - Helsinki Final Act, 1982 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Holocaust, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - House Subcommittee on Asian Affairs, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - House Subcommittee on Human Rights, 1983 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Humanitas correspondence and newsletters, 1981-1985 and undated (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Human rights, 1981 and undated (Box-folder 34: 2)
  - Human Rights Internet, 1982 (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - Hannum, Hurst, 1983 October (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Index on Censorship, undated (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Institute for Contemporary Studies, 1983 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Institute for Educational Affairs, 1982 (Box-folder 34: 7)
  - Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1984 (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Inter-American Dialogue, 1984 (Box-folder 34: 9)
  - International Covenants on Human Rights, 1976 (Box-folder 34: 10)
  - International Human Rights Day, 1983 December (Box-folder 34: 11)
  - International Institute of Geopolitics, 1984 (Box-folder 34: 12)
  - International League for Human Rights, 1984 (Box-folder 34: 13)
  - International Parliamentary Group, 1985 (Box-folder 34: 14)
  - International Policy Report, 1983 (Box-folder 34: 15)
  - Italian community, undated (Box-folder 34: 16)
  - "Journalism and Nuclear Power," by Bernard L. Cohen, undated (Box-folder 34: 17)
  - Italian resistance, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 34: 18)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, undated (Box-folder 34: 19)
  - Keston College, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 34: 20)
  - Lawyers Committee for International Human Rights, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 34: 21)
  - Lelio Basso Foundation, 1984 (Box-folder 34: 22)
  - Lewis, Flora, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 34: 23)
  - Maïs, Jean and Lucien Trong, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - McCloskey, Paul, 1983 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - Media, 1983 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Médecins du monde, 1983-1984, undated (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Murphy, R.W., 1983 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Nemec, Jan, 1984 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - Pacem Productions, 1985 (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - Panzini, Tiberio, 1945 April (Box-folder 35: 8)
    Translation of letter from Panzini
  - Pavarotti, Luciano, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 35: 9)
  - Permanent Peoples' Tribunal, 1984 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1983 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - Pope Pius XII, undated (Box-folder 35: 12)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1984 December 10 (Box-folder 35: 13)
    Remarks on Human Rights Day
  - Refugees International, 1985 (Box-folder 35: 14)
  - Refugee Policy Group, 1983 (Box-folder 35: 15)
  - Religion in Communist areas, 1983 (Box-folder 35: 16)
  - Reston, James, 1983 (Box-folder 35: 17)
  - Rohrabacher, Dana, undated (Box-folder 35: 18)
  - Sagan, Leonard, 1976 (Box-folder 35: 19)
  - Sikh Foundation USA, 1984 (Box-folder 35: 20)
  - Survival International USA, 1985 (Box-folder 35: 21)
  - State Department, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 35: 22)
  - Torture by Governments, 1984 (Box-folder 35: 23)
  - United Nations, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 35: 24-26)
  - UNESCO, 1970 and undated (Box-folder 35: 27)
  - Wilson Center, undated (Box-folder 35: 28)
  - World federalism, undated (Box-folder 35: 29)
  - World Without War Council, 1984 (Box-folder 35: 30)
  - Lombardi, Riccardo letter to GS, 1977 October 15 (Box-folder 35: 31)
- Amnesty International, 1971-1976
  - American prisoners, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - Amnesty Action, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - Latin American prisoners, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 3)
  - Lawyers, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 4)
  - Libya, 1972, 1977 (Box-folder 36: 5)
  - Lilienthal, Sally, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 6)
  - Lister, George, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 7)
  - Lithuania, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 8)
  - Little, Joan, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36: 9)
    Correspondence with the Grateful Dead (Robert Hunter) on a song in honor of Little
  - Lofton, John, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 10)
  - Malawi, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 36: 11)
  - Mali, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 36: 12)
  - Medical committee, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 36: 13)
  - Media correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 36: 14)
  - Media publicity, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36: 15)
  - News media list, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 16)
  - Addresses, Europe, undated (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - Alexander, Archie S., Jr., 1975 (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - American Bar Association, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1973, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37: 5)
  - American Indians, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 6)
  - American Professors for Peace in the Middle East, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 7)
  - Correspondence with other Amnesty offices, 1974-1976
    - Los Angeles office, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 8)
    - San Francisco office, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 9)
    - Mexico, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 10)
    - New York office, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 11)
    - Southern California office, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 12)
    - Western Regional Office, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 37: 13)
  - Angola, undated (Box-folder 37: 14)
  - Annual report, 1973 (Box-folder 37: 15)
  - Applicants, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 16)
  - Arab League, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37: 17)
  - Argentina, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37: 18)
  - Armijo, Roland, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 19)
  - Arms control, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37: 20)
  - Aruda, Marcos, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 21)
  - Assets and liabilities, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 22)
  - Baez, Joan, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 23)
  - Bangladesh, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 24)
  - Barton, David (Indochina Resource Center), 1975 (Box-folder 37: 25)
  - Bay Area Council for Soviet Jewry, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 26)
  - Beyers, Charlotte, 1975-1975 (Box-folder 37: 27)
  - Biafra, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 28)
  - Boards of Directors, Amnesty International USA, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 29)
  - Bolivia, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 30)
  - Booklist, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 31)
  - Brazil, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 37: 32)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 37: 33)
  - Bulgaria, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 34)
  - California, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 37: 35)
  - Cameroon, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 36)
  - Chávez, César, 1971 (Box-folder 37: 37)
  - Chicago office, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37: 38)
  - China, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 39)
  - Church, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 40)
  - CIA, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 41)
  - Commons, Stanley B., 1975 (Box-folder 37: 42)
  - Conflict Resolution Conference, undated (Box-folder 37: 43)
  - Conscientious objectors, 1973 (Box-folder 37: 44)
  - Constitutional court, undated (Box-folder 37: 45)
  - Contacts, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 37: 46)
  - Card file, undated
    Contains index cards on AI members, donors and correspondents
    - A-L (Box 38)
    - M-Z (Box 39)
- Correspondence, 1982, undated
  - Unidentified, circa 1982 (Box-folder 40: 1)
    Includes two photographs of GS
  - Aurora Foundation, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - Amnesty International, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 3)
  - Personal, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - Friends of Amnesty, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 5-6)
  - Menil, Dominique de, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 7)
  - Campaign for Abolition of Torture, 1982 August (Box-folder 40: 8)
  - GS's personal stationery, undated (Box-folder 40: 9-10)
  - Camp Minniwanca, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 11)
- GS curriculum vitae, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 12)
- Amnesty International, 1972-1981
  - Annual general meeting, 1982 (Box-folder 40: 13)
  - Year of St. Francis fundraiser, 1981 (Box-folder 40: 14)
  - Campaign for the Abolition of Torture, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - Campaign strategy, Amnesty International Luxembourg, 1975 (Box-folder 41: 2)
  - Carlson, Joel, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 41: 3)
  - Celebrities, 1975 (Box-folder 41: 4)
  - Center for Teaching about Peace and War, 1974 (Box-folder 41: 5)
  - Chad, 1975 (Box-folder 41: 6)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 41: 7-8)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1976 (Box-folder 41: 9)
  - Crazy department, 1974 and undated (Box-folder 41: 10)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1975 (Box-folder 41: 11)
  - DeFunis, Marco, 1970s (Box-folder 41: 12)
  - Delbruk, Max, 1976 (Box-folder 41: 13)
  - Curricula vitae of Hermann Schwember and Carmen Baura Rodriguez Cortes, 1974 (Box-folder 41: 14)
  - Detroit, 1976 (Box-folder 41: 15)
  - Diller, Sanford, 1975 (Box-folder 41: 16)
  - Diplomatic list, 1974 November (Box-folder 41: 17)
  - Dominican Republic, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41: 18)
  - Ecuador, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41: 19)
  - Educational projects, undated (Box-folder 41: 20)
  - El Salvador, undated (Box-folder 41: 21)
  - Ennals, Martin, 1975 (Box-folder 41: 22)
  - Group 34, 1975 (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - Group meetings, 1974 (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - Human rights, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 42: 3)
  - India, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - Indochina, 1972 and undated (Box-folder 42: 5)
  - International Council Meeting, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 42: 6-7)
  - Ireland, 1976 (Box-folder 42: 8)
  - Italy, 1975 and undated (Box-folder 42: 9)
  - Japan, 1975 (Box-folder 42: 10)
  - Japan Christian Activity News, 1975 (Box-folder 42: 11)
  - Jewish Community Relations Council, undated (Box-folder 42: 12)
  - Jones, Tom and Katie, 1975 (Box-folder 42: 13)
  - Korea Campaign for Bishop Chi Hak-Sun, 1974 and undated (Box-folder 42: 14)
  - Latin American scholars, 1975 (Box-folder 42: 15)
  - Equatorial Guinea, 1975 (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - Ethiopia, 1974 (Box-folder 43: 2)
  - Financial, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 43: 3)
  - Fleming, Amalia, Lady, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    Includes letters from Fleming
  - Freedom of the press, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 43: 5)
  - Freund, Marketa, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 43: 6)
  - Gabon, 1975 (Box-folder 43: 7)
  - Germany, 1974 (Box-folder 43: 8)
  - Grunwald, Hanna, 1974 (Box-folder 43: 9)
  - Guatemala, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 43: 10)
  - Haiti, undated (Box-folder 43: 11)
  - Handbook for Groups and How to Free Your Prisoner, 1974 (Box-folder 43: 12)
  - Harkin amendment, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 43: 13)
  - Hawk, David, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 43: 14)
  - Heads of state, circa 1978 (Box-folder 43: 15)
  - Holtzmann, Elizabeth, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 43: 16)
  - Korea (South), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 43: 17)
  - London office, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 43: 18)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Australia group, 1974 (Box-folder 44: 2)
  - Financial statements, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 44: 3)
  - Foreign sections, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 44: 4)
  - Ginzton, Edward, 1976 (Box-folder 44: 5)
  - Gische, David, 1974 (Box-folder 44: 6)
  - Green, Carol, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 44: 7)
  - Groups, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 44: 8)
  - Amnesty Action, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 45: 1)